Eduir BrazónSystems Engineer

<u>+584148636110</u>

M eduirbrazon@gmail.com

Eduirbr

eduirbrazon

Profile

I am a backend and API developer with experience in both public and freelance environments. I have worked on creating and improving APIs for mobile applications, as well as building Telegram bots for digitizing documents. Always open to learning and contributing to the team.

Formación

Universidad de Oriente Núcleo Monagas Ingeniería de Sistemas 2010-2024

Experience

Tecfin 212 / Teclot

(October 2022 - June 2023, December 2023 - Present) Maturín, Monagas, Venezuela

Software Developer / Back-End Participated in the initial development of kiosqo.com, focusing on bug fixes and implementing critical functionalities. Continued improving and maintaining the project in its current reengineering.

Skills

Languages:
Python, Go, JavaScript, Dart,
HTML, C++

Frameworks and tools: Django, Django Rest Framework, Fiber, Flutter, Git, PostgreSQL, SQLite, DBeaver

DCTI - Dirección de Ciencias Tecnologías e Innovación

Maturín, Monagas, Venezuela Intern (May 2022 - December 2022)

Made contributions to the APIs of a proposed system and assisted in the construction of an API Gateway for a proposed system.

Programming Analyst (June 2023 - August 2024): Developed the backend of two versions of a supply management system and Provided Git and Go training to the new hires.

Courses

Python Course
Go Course
C++ Course
Fundamentals of Scrum
Git

Freelancer

(January 2023 - Present)

API Development: Developed APIs for mobile applications. Created a Telegram bot for digitizing documents. Made improvements to various existing APIs and developed APIs from scratch.

Languages

Spanish - Native English - Intermediate

Aptitudes

Teamwork
Effective Communication
Adaptability
Problem-solving
Creativity
Leadership